<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rina Foygel Barber</title>
    <link>https://rinafb.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rina Foygel Barber</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://rinafb.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Group</title>
      <link>https://rinafb.github.io/group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rinafb.github.io/group/</guid>
      <description>Group members  Zhimei Ren, postdoctoral scholar Yonghoon Lee, PhD student Wanrong Zhu, PhD student (co-advised with Wei-Biao Wu) Yu Gui, PhD student Rohan Hore, PhD student Young-Joo Yun, MS student Qiqi Liu, MS student Heming Liu, MS student Xiaomeng Wang, BA/MS student  PhD alumni  Ang Li (2017), Data Scientist, Twitter Wooseok Ha (2018), Postdoctoral Scholar, Foundations of Data Analysis Institute, University of California, Berkeley Fan Yang (2019), Junior Quantitative Researcher, Akuna Ran Dai (2020), Assistant Professor, Department of Biostatistics, University of Nebraska Medical Center Haoyang Liu (2020), Hudson River Trading Byol Kim (2021), Postdoctoral Scholar, Department of Statistics, University of Washington  Information for prospective students I typically advise one PhD student per year and several Master&amp;rsquo;s students per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://rinafb.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rinafb.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Publications &amp;amp; preprints (organized by topic)  Distribution-free inference   Training-conditional coverage for distribution-free predictive inference. (Code.)
Michael Bian and Rina Foygel Barber. arXiv:2205.03647
  Conformal prediction beyond exchangeability. (Code; Slides.)
Rina Foygel Barber, Emmanuel J. Candès, Aaditya Ramdas, and Ryan Tibshirani. arXiv:2202.13415
  Black box tests for algorithmic stability.
Byol Kim and Rina Foygel Barber. arXiv:2111.15546
  Distribution-free inference for regression: discrete, continuous, and in between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://rinafb.github.io/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rinafb.github.io/software/</guid>
      <description>This page lists software packages only.
For code to implement methods and reproduce experiments from individual papers, links to code are placed next to each paper title (go to the Research tab).
 SEMID: Identifiability of linear structural equation models R package for determining whether the parameters of mixed graphical model are identifiable from the resulting data distribution. (With Mathias Drton.)
Related papers:
Half-trek criterion for generic identifiability of linear structural equation models, Rina Foygel, Jan Draisma, Mathias Drton (arxiv link).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://rinafb.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rinafb.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>All course websites are on Canvas.
Current courses  Stat 24400: Statistical Theory and Methods I (Autumn 2021). Syllabus. Stat 34300: Applied Linear Statistical Methods (Autumn 2021). Syllabus. Stat 27850/30850: Multiple Testing, Modern Inference, and Replicability (Winter 2022). Syllabus.  Past courses  Stat 41520: Topics in Selective Inference (Autumn 2020), co-taught with Will Fithian (UC Berkeley).
Course website.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
